



# Silva Keci

**Date of birth:** 20/06/2000 | **Nationality:** Albanian | **Gender:** Female |

Phone number: (+355) 0692122415 (Mobile) | Email address:

silvakeci05@gmail.com | LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/public-profile/settings?trk=d flagship3 profile self view public profile

Whatsapp Messenger: 0692122415

Address: Tirane, Albania, 1001, Tirana, Albania (Home)

#### ABOUT ME

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for the technology industry. I have excellent mathematical logic skills, enabling me to find the most effective and optimal solution to the problem. I am seeing a part-time / full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2019 - 14/07/2023 Tirana, Albania

### **ENGINEERING MATHEMATICAL AND INFORMATICS** University of Tirana

- Computer Architecture
- Data Structures and Algorithms
- Advanced Calculus
- Discrete Mathematics
- Linear Algebra
- · Probability and Statistics

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/02/2023 - CURRENT Tirana, Albania

### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER GRANIT**

As a software developer at GranIT, I develop my skills in:

- React Native (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Mobile Application Development
- UI/UX Design
- Problem-Solving and Troubleshooting
- Git version control

01/11/2022 - 01/02/2023 Tirana, Albania

#### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** INTESA SANPAOLO BANK

As a software developer at Intesa Sanpaolo Bank, I work with:

- Java Programming language with Spring Boot framework.
- MySQL Database
- Git version control
- Jira project management tool

01/04/2021 - 01/06/2021

### FULL-STACK DEVELOPER ELITE ACADEMY (INTERNSHIP)

As a software developer at Elite Academy, I work with:

- C# Programming language with Spring Boot framework.
- MySQL Database

- Git version control
- React Js

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ALBANIAN** 

Other language(s): **ENGLISH** 

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **DRIVING LICENCE**

**Driving Licence:** B